wcb.com 2012-07-30

# FACTS

                                                                                                                            Rev 03/12
                       WHAT DOES WEST COAST BANK
FACTS                  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                      consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                      how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                      • Social Security number and credit scores
                      • Transaction or loss history and checking account information
                      • Account balances and mortgage rates and payments
How?                  All financial companies need to share customer personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customer
                      personal information; the reasons West Coast Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit
                      this sharing.
                                                                           Does West Coast                  Can you limit
 Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                               Bank share?                  this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as (1) to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                                      YES                          NO
account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or
report to credit bureaus, or (2) as permitted by law
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                      YES                         YES
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                    YES                         YES
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                      YES                         YES
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                       NO                    We Don’t Share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                                   YES                         YES
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                     NO                    We Don’t Share
To limit               Call 800-895-3345
                       Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
our sharing            sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in
                       this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?             Call 800-895-3345

 Page 2
What we do
How does West Coast Bank         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we
protect my personal information? use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
                                 computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does West Coast Bank         We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information? • Open an account or apply for a loan
                                 • Show us your driver’s license or show us your government issued ID
                                 • Use your credit or debit card
                                 We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                 affiliates, or other companies
Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                 • s haring for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your
                                    creditworthiness
                                 • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                 • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                 State laws and invidivuals companies may give you additional rights to
                                 limit sharing.
What happens when I limit
sharing for an account I hold    Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                 nonfinancial companies.
                                 • Our affiliates include financial companies such as West Coast Trust.
Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                                 and nonfinancial companies.
                                 • West Coast Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
                                 • Nonaffiliates we share with can include companies such as mortgage
                                    companies. This sharing will occur in the event you apply for a first mortgage
                                    loan.
Joint Marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                 market financial products or services to you.
                                 • Our joint marketing partners include leasing companies, securities
                                    broker-dealers, credit card companies, and merchant card processors.
